<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: retrospective | Bob Jiang Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://bobjiang.github.com/blog/categories/retrospective/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bobjiang.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-03-13T16:44:12+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://bobjiang.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Bob Jiang]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[测试人员应该参加回顾会议吗?]]></title>
    <link href="http://bobjiang.github.com/blog/2013/02/07/keep-testers-out-of-retrospective/"/>
    <updated>2013-02-07T16:34:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://bobjiang.github.com/blog/2013/02/07/keep-testers-out-of-retrospective</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today I read a monthly news from Mike Cohn, and it is very interesting. Should we exclude testers from retrospective? I don't think so, what's your opinion?</p>

<p>I've decided we should kick all the testers out of sprint retrospectives. We don't need them. They aren't really part of the team, anyway. They think differently and their issues aren't really the same issues faced by the real team.</p>

<p><img src="/images/keepout.jpg"></p>

<!-- more -->


<p>How'd that sound? It was hard to even type so hopefully it took you pretty far aback.</p>

<p>However, I occasionally hear exactly that same message except about product owners. I can't think of a single good reason why a team would want to hold a retrospective without the product owner present. I can think of many bad reasons why they may want to--but each of those should be the topic of a retrospective!</p>

<p>If you're tempted to run a sprint retrospective without your product owner, I strongly suggest you think about why. Product owners are full, first-class team members. It's critical that they participate in retrospectives and they are as open as everyone else to hearing things they can do to improve. Teams that don't include their product owner tend to suffer from us vs. them thinking that is almost always harmful to the project.</p>

<p>I hope your next retrospective is successful. To help that happen, make sure the product owner is there.</p>

<p>Included below are two links that can help. The first is a description of the sprint retrospective. It briefly summarizes my preferred approach to that meeting--a <strong>start, stop, and continue technique</strong>. The second is a link to a review of the Agile Retrospectives book by Esther Derby and Diana Larsen, which should be required reading for every ScrumMaster.</p>

<h1>Sprint Retrospective  </h1>

<p>No matter how good a Scrum team is, there is always opportunity to improve. Although a good Scrum team will be constantly looking for improvement opportunities, the team should set aside a brief, dedicated period at the end of each sprint to...</p>

<p><a href="http://www.mountaingoatsoftware.com/scrum/sprint-retrospective">Continue Reading...</a></p>

<h1>Agile Retrospectives:Making Good Teams Great </h1>

<p>Excellent advice for those desiring more frequent, shorter, better retrospectives. One of the challenges facing an agile team that holds a retrospective at the end of each one– to four–week iteration is how to keep the meetings fresh. When done...</p>

<p><a href="http://www.mountaingoatsoftware.com/reviews/agile-retrospectives">Continue Reading...</a></p>

<p>Origin from Mike Cohn's Blog</p>

<hr />

<p>最后揭晓答案:<br/>
在Scrum中,Sprint Retrospective会议要求全体团队成员参加,包括Scrum Master, Product Owner, Team(这里当然包含测试人员)以及其他相关人.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
